Those who ceaselessly hone the art
of killing are known as masters.
These lethal abilities, dutifully
passed down through many generations,
have become what are
called modified bloodlines.
This is the story of one such master,
Hikaru Gero of the Poison Clan
and his greatest challenge yet,
to get married.
No mama, lots of time?
Run fun, fun, fun you So cool, no!
Kill or kiss
Let's go!
Kill a kiss, can't kill a kiss!
I'm Mei Kinosaki, I'm just your perfectly
average everyday marriage swindler!
Lately, I've been doing an awesome
job of helping Gato look for a bride!
At least, that was the original plan.
So what am I doing here?
This wasn't exactly in
the job description.
This guy here is Piichi.
He started out as our enemy.
But then we found out he was
after the Beastmaster too.
So we've been working together.
He's scary good.
And kind of a freak.
His combat skills are off the charts.
And even after an explosion
should have killed him.
One 10-hour nap later, he's good as new.
His dream was to open a
cafe with his girlfriend.
And since their customers won't be
safe with a bunch of psychos around,
he swore to take down the Beast Clan.
Talk about a dangerous guy.
Think the store leads somewhere important?
He's not even a master.
But he found a shortcut to
the Clan's headquarters.
Plus, he killed some elite group called
the Five Beastars in mere seconds.
So, they're done.
Guess the way is clear.
After you.
Is that the Karate Bear from earlier?
Which means that guy must be...
The Beastmaster?
Byakko, buy me ten seconds.
Modified bloodline, flash flash!
Stop!
Master Toshiro, I won't let you down.
Even among the monsters of the underworld,
there are masters who are
shunned by the Beast Clan, Prius.
Look at them.
Can't even forge bonds
with their partners.
Why are they a part of this clan?
I heard at one point they were tough, but
these days they're just playing dress-up.
Mom, what's wrong?
It'll be okay, sweetie.
Mommy just made a little mistake at work.
It's not fair.
You need treatment.
Why won't they help?
It's all right.
It's my fault I'm hurt.
Remember, the hospital, only Beastmasters
with partners can be healed there.
Outcasts like us aren't permitted.
Can't we try?
Yaku...
I'm so sorry.
She needs some medicine!
I'll get you the rest!
I'm begging you!
Mom...
are you...
When she died, why her?
It's too much.
I feel the same way.
I can't stand this shitty world.
Not a damn thing about it.
How every little thing is tied
down by these meaningless rules.
But all the trash is prey for us.
Stick with me, kid, I swear.
We're gonna devour this world, you and me.
I lost everything.
But Master Toshiro found me.
Gave me a reason to live.
I'd do anything for him.
Maybe we should serve
wild game at our cafe.
A one-hit KO?
I'm not really about fighting for
justice or anything like that.
But, Mr.
Beastmaster, if you plan
on sacrificing people,
I'm gonna have to stop you.
Hey!
How long are you gonna lie there?
Forgive me.
I failed, Master Toshiro.
I wasn't talking about that.
Look, it's complete.
The blood from 93 major and
minor branches of the Beast Clan.
As well as six Masters, including
Gatos, went into creating this.
An impure abomination made just for you.
The Frankenbeast.
Hyakko!
You should see your faces!
How dumbfounded you are by
the sheer power before you!
I regret to inform you all.
The moment you challenged me in a caldera
lake, you forfeited any chance of victory!
All clear. Come on.
We should keep moving.
I think I'm going to need a bigger knife.
There's got to be something
around here I can use. Let's see.
Something large and heavy
and good for stabbing.
This ought to do.
A giant skeleton, but from what?
Oh, I see.
So it's fast and strong.
Not only that.
Apparently it's got these abnormal
muscles and bones, both tough and light.
On top of all that,
its nervous system seems to let
it reshape its morphology at will.
He must have put a lot of
work into making this thing.
So, how about this?
Worth a shot.
If I can blind it and circle around
from behind, I can deal a fatal blow.
It predicted what I'd do?
No way.
It read my movements.
I might have to sacrifice
an arm to block in time.
I hope this doesn't hurt.
But why why can't I kill her?
Ever since I had a knife,
I've never had a problem killing
anyone, including masters.
Right
there's really
no mystery to it.
Like I said,
Kyako's got a custom blend
of master bloodlines and
that includes a a healthy
amount of your very own.
You're fighting an upgraded
version of yourself.
Better in every single way.
EG!
Do you mind answering that? Right now?
It's my girlfriend calling.
You there, Piichi?
You won't believe what's happening.
Did the Beast Clan assassins get her?
Get this.
King Goose just made an announcement.
They're going on tour!
Celebrating ten years!
Yay!
Aomori, Aichi, Fukuoka, and the Budokan,
but getting tickets is a literal nightmare.
Anyway, just wanted to tell you.
You'd better clear your schedule, mister.
Because I'd hate to go by myself.
Love ya.
Ha! That's it?
I waited to kill you for that?
Could the little airhead
be any more clueless?
The next time she'll be reunited with
her psycho boyfriend will be in a grave.
Do it.
Marin, she knows exactly what's going on,
what protecting our
ordinary life means to me.
That's what gets me fired up.
Are you for real?
It's a little too late to start
taking this fight seriously!
I'll crush him.
Edgey!
How can I beat this thing?
I don't make up for height,
weight, but we're talking to this.
Maybe the joints are weak.
Do monsters have accurate tendons?
Oh, what about crucial ligaments?
You really can't walk without those.
What will Marin think about all this?
I hope she gets those kangoos together.
A chimera lunch special.
As long as I can remember.
My brain's always been a jumbled mess.
But right now, I can use that.
My thoughts are messier than
ever, and deeper, and freer.
and I'm going to unleash
every last one of them.
What's with him?
One stupid phone call.
And he's transformed.
Mind if I borrow your right arm?
He got a step ahead of my prediction.
Now I get it.
This is how you move your limbs.
I'm getting the hang of it.
But you know, I think I'm going
to need a little more firepower.
How about this?
Yeah, this should work.
I'm losing control over my nervous system.
I won't be beaten by him.
He's a nobody!
We're gonna devour this world, you and me.
Sorry about this. Nothing personal.
But I've got to stop your boss.
Guy's crazy.
That was nuts!
Hey, are you okay, Piichi?
I'll be good in a bit.
I just need a five-minute nap.
For real?
Master Toshiro, please drain my blood.
Every last drop.
Becoming one with you would be an honor.
The greatest.
I've got you.
We'd better get out of here now.
Is that blood?
Okay, Byakko.
It's you and me against
the world full of prey.
Let's devour every last one of them!
Peach is in bad shape.
He's not going anywhere.
The exit isn't far. No choice.
Gotta run, Bart!
We're not done playing yet.
Sorry I'm late. What'd we miss?
Perfect timing.
What's up Water Master?
I'm glad you could make it out.
I'm charging you extra
for that Ushio boost.
Hands work but I'm still not 100% yet.
It won't be long.
Kinosaki?
I know this is outside
your job description.
I apologize but I promise we'll make this
quick so you and I can get
back to dating. Lessons? Yeah,
the Beast Clan is one of
the five great families.
The branch families tune their
modified bloodlines allowing them
to communicate with their animal
partners by enhancing a single.
physical traits.
However, for the main family, the
Dogo lineage doesn't have limits.
Our limbs,
our organs, even our five senses.
They're tuned to perfection and
have the powers of the entire
animal kingdom, making us monsters.
That's the origin of our
modified bloodline. Beastblood.
Sheep, Goat, Deer, Camel,
Donkey, Hippo, Llama, Buffalo, Noon,
Okapi, Kangaroo, Giant Anteater, Taper,
Fox, Tanooki, Boar, Rabbit, Weasel,
Mark, Sink, Stove, Honor, Crisco, Spline,
Squirrel, Squirrel, Koala, Amadillo,
Porcupine, Sloth, Seelight, Soul, Furzeeal,
Walrus, Sea, Octopus, Shrine, Nautiland!
93 species plus six masters makes
a cocktail of 99 bloodlines!
The great Byakko!
An impure beast that allowed Byakko
to unleash her full potential.
But in the end, it was
meant for one thing.
To be prey!
They're just an offering,
so that I, Toshiro Dogo, can
become the ultimate beast.
Kichi!
Fujio!
Kiro!
What a heartwarming twist!
team-ups always have me on the
edge of my seat but turns out
none of you are anything special
what's your problem
you better wipe
that look off your face or I'm
gonna take my sweet time with you as
long as we all work together we've got We
can bust out of this place, no problem!
Forget it.
Everyone can feel it in their blood.
We can still hear the screams of our
partners consumed by the Beastmaster.
Even if we did manage to escape, we'll
never get away from that monster.
And the weakest member of the
clan isn't going to change that.
It'll only hurt a short while.
Soon it'll all be over.
Until then, we must clear our minds.
Three doses?
But Gato...
Toxin! Triple dose!
He's barely conscious.
You don't know when to quit, do you?
I mean, three doses?
After an OD like that,
you gotta hurt like hell!
I'll put you out of your misery, though.
All those years thinning the family herd.
For this power of slaughtering
them was worth it!
Look out, Gato!
I was used to eating alone.
Getting to share a meal felt really nice.
Jack!
An overdose means certain death.
But fighting to find a bride
has led to something unexpected.
A mutation of sorts.
The eyesight of a falcon,
the jump of a kangaroo,
and the deadliness of a cassowary.
I'll rip you apart before you
have time to blink! Thank you.
I want marriage.
I'm out of the wine.
Get this with poor liberty.
This is your love.
If I getparado.
Should've walked away.
Then I studied.
When I says to you.
We're back.
I come on.
You know I'm going to be good afectude.
You know I'm going to be good
and you're going to be good.
I'm going to be good for you.
We are super happy and we are.
We are too old.
I'll be creepy.
Oh make that noise.
Dancing with you. I'm eating a mess.
I'm eating a tô.
Thank you.
One-on-one? I don't think so.
My bloodlust ran out ages ago.
Blood is not a curse.
Next time, heart and soul.